http://www.dtsearch.co.uk/about/privacy-policy.aspx

Menu
Home ProductsOverviews & Price ListdtSearch Desktop/NetworkdtSearch EnginedtSearch WebdtSearch PublishdtSearch File ConvertersdtSearch Engine for LinuxUser Thesaurus PlusLanguage PacksStemming Language SelectorStemming TesterList AnalyserDatabase Indexer365 IndexerREST ServerSearch-as-a-Service BuyResellers Case Studies SupportContact Support/RegisterTraining About|NewsNewsdtSearch UKdtSearch CorpdtSearch HistoryTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyContact Us Blog
Privacy Policy
IntroductiondtSearch UK is committed to protecting your privacy. We recognise our responsibility to keep confidential at all times any personal data (also  referred to as Personally Identifiable Information) about you which we acquire.
Data ControllerdtSearch UK (referred to as “we”, “our” in this policy) is a trading name of Electronart Design Ltd., who is the “data controller” (for the purposes of the (GDPR) General Data Protection Regulations) of all personal data collected and used about dtSearch UK customers. Electronart Design Ltd is registered in England CRN: 01796515 and registered office at 27 Shaftesbury Centre, Barlby Road, London, W10 6BN.
Collection of Personal DataTo enable us to process your order, enquiry or product registration we will typically acquire personal data which includes your name, your e-mail, your address, and credit/debit card or other payment information. This personal data may come directly from emails from you or via forms on our website or via resellers or suppliers that have taken your order or enquiry.
Use and sharing of Personal DataWe use the information which you provide us to process your order, registration or enquiry and to provide technical support. We may also email news of new products or services, or email developer information such as beta releases or sample code if you have opted-in to these services. You can opt-out any time by clicking an unsubscribe or opt-out link or by contacting us by email or via the Contact Us form.
Some details are shared with credit/debit card processing companies or other credit checking agencies when we process your order. We may also share relevant information with our product suppliers and resellers outside the EU to provide technical support. Subject to the above, dtSearch UK will not disclose personal data to third parties, or make any use of it, without your permission (unless we are required to do so by statute or by an authorised body in order to aid the investigation or prevention of crime).
We will only process your personal data where we have a legal basis to do so. The legal basis will depend on the reasons we have collected and need to use your personal data for.
We will not retain your data for longer than is necessary. To determine the retention period, we consider the purposes for which we process it and to meet our legal and commercial obligations (e.g. HMRC, software license agreements) or to deal with complaints, queries or to protect our legal rights.
When we no longer need your personal data, we will securely delete or destroy it. We will also aim over time to minimize the personal data that we use, and if we can anonymise your personal data so that it can no longer identify you.
SecuritydtSearch UK is committed to protecting the security of your personal data. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure.
CookiesThis website uses cookies which are text files used by your computer's browser, that store visitor session data. You can usually modify your browser settings to prevent this happening. However, by disabling cookies, or certain types of cookie, you may hinder your user experience on this and other websites.  Cookies, by themselves, do not identify the individual user. Cookies are commonly used on the Internet and do not harm your system.
Some cookies used on this website are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its feature. Without these cookies services like shopping baskets cannot be provided.
Some cookies used on this website collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don't collect information that identifies a visitor, the information collected is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how a website works.
These cookies may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.
Cookies may also be used to improve the user experience and to enable some of the functionality provided by this website.
Some cookies may be placed by third party service providers who perform some of these functions (or other services) for us. Cookies are used on this website for the following third party services: Google Analytics, Facebook Button, Twitter Follow button, YouTube videos. Some of these services may be used to track your behaviour on other websites and we have no control over this.
By continuing to use this website without adjusting your browser's cookie settings, you agree that we can place these cookies on your device.
Telephone Call RecordingWe use digital voicemail to record customer messages and may also record telephone conversations during calls to customers or suppliers to assist us to serve you better.
Fax messages Please note that in common with other companies we typically convert incoming fax messages to PDF or similar digital format for easy distribution within our organisation, and these may also be transmitted over the internet to remote working employees or our suppliers outside the EU. You should not consider that Fax is a secure medium to send personal or sensitive information (e.g. Credit Card data) although we endevour to keep such messages secure within our organisation.
Your Data Protection RightsBy law you can (except under certain circumstances) :
Request information about what personal data that we hold about you, and why we are holding or using it.
Request access to your personal data.
Request correction of the personal data that we hold about you.
Request erasure of your personal data.
Request transfer of your personal data in an electronic form to you or to another party (commonly known as a right to “data portability”). We can provide this in .csv format only.
If you want to exercise any of these rights, please submit a request using the Contact Us form or Support/Registraton form or by post to Customer Service at our registered office. You will not have to pay a fee unless your request is unreasonable or excessive and this will be actioned within 30 days.
If you have any concerns please contact us, you can also report concerns to the Information Commissioners Office
Changes to Privacy PolicyOur Privacy Policy may change from time to time, you should check this notice for the date is was last updated.
Last Updated: 19 May 2018
(Please note your rights under GDPR listed above come into effect 25 May 2018.)
Youtube
Facebook
Twitter
